Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Departments, 1985-2006; Series II
  - Member Services Department
    - Member Publications
      - Essays in Celebration of the First Fifty Years, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 397)
      - ATLA Organizationald and Membership Directory, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - ATLA Web Site
      - Correspondence regarding proposal for Vanderbilt University to host site, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 398)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 1996 May/Jul-Dec (Box 11, Folder 399)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 1996 Jul-Sep, Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 400)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 401)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 402)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 403)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 404)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 405)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 406)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 407)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 408)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 409)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 410)
      - Previous Weekly News Updates (Printed 11/11/05.), 2002 (Box 12, Folder 411)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 2002 (Box 12, Folder 412)
      - Previous Messages From the Executive Director (Printed 11/11/05.), 2003 (Box 12, Folder 413)
      - Weekly News Updates, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 414)
      - Weekly News Updates, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 415)
      - Weekly News Updates, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 416)
      - Pages from site saved on December 1, 1998 (Printed on 9/8/06), 1998 Dec 1 (Box 12, Folder 417)
      - Preservation Services pages from site saved on December 1, 1998 (Printed on 9/8/06), 1998 Dec 1 (Box 12, Folder 418)
      - Selections on Microfilm from the Yale Day Missions Collection, Subject Headings, Preservation Services Pages from site saved on December 1, 1998 (Printed on 9/8/06), 1998 Dec 1 (Box 12, Folder 419)
      - Reference Desk Pages from site samplings saved on December 1, 1998 (Printed on 9/8/06), 1998 Dec 1 (Box 12, Folder 420)
      - Staff Directory pages saved on March 4, 2000 (Printed on 9/8/06), 2000 Mar 4 (Box 12, Folder 421)
      - Printout of pages regarding Center for Electronic Resources in Theology and Religion (CERTR), 2000 Mar (Box 12, Folder 422)
      - ATLAS pages from site samplings saved on December 6, 2000 (Printed on 9/8/06), 2000 Dec 6 (Box 12, Folder 423)
      - ATLA Member Spotlight from site sampling saved on February 2, 2001 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 424)
      - Library Consultation pages from site sampling saved on February 2, 2001 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 425)
      - Grants and Awards pages from a site sampling saved on February 2, 2001 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 426)
      - Management Issues Seminar information from site sampling saved on February 2, 2001 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 427)
      - ATLA CERTR pages from site sampling saved on February 2, 2001 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 428)
      - Site samplings from pages saved on July 22, 2001 (Showing new site design) (Printed on 9/15/06), 2001 Jul 22 (Box 12, Folder 429)
      - Site samplings saved on May 24, 2004 (Printed on 9/15/06), 2004 May 24 (Box 12, Folder 430)
      - About Us, List of Services, List of Departments, Staff Member Titles, and Directions to ATLA (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 431)
      - Staff Directory (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 432)
      - Conference Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05), 2006 Jun 21-24 (Box 12, Folder 433)
      - ATLANTIS/Hosted Discussion Groups Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 434)
      - Membership Information and Applications (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 435)
      - Awards, Grants and Scholarships Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 436)
      - ATLA Group Catalog on OCLC WorldCat (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 437)
      - ATLA International Collaboration Database (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 438)
      - "About the ATLA Special Committee of the Association for International Collaboration" (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 439)
      - ATLA-ICC Bibliography for International Seminary/Bible School Libraries (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 440)
      - ATLA Member Hurricane Relief Efforts Information (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 441)
      - ATLA Selected Religion Web Sites Project (ATSRW) (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 442)
      - Cooperative Digital Resources Initiative (CDRI) (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 443)
      - First Search Consortium, NACO/CONSER Funnel Projects, On Demand Filming, and Serials Exchange (ASE) (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 444)
      - Divisions and Committees (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 445)
      - Collection Evaluation and Development Interest Group (CEAD) Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 446)
      - ATLA Technical Services Web (Website of ATLA's Technical Services Section) (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 447)
      - Librarian's Tools and Member Directories (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 448)
      - Professional Development Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 449)
      - Publications Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05, 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 450)
      - Preservation Department Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 451)
      - Product Pages (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 452)
      - Retrospective Indexing Project (RIP) Quarterly Reports (Printed from web site 11/11/05), 2002 Sep- 2005 Aug (Box 12, Folder 453)
      - Thesaurus Revisions (Printed from web site 11/11/05.), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 454)
      - Advertising Opportunities, Endowment Fund, and Interactive Conference Facility (ICF) Printed from web site 11/11/05., 2005 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 455)
      - Printout of Special 60th Anniversary Pages (Printed from web site on 5/26/06), 2006 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 456)
      - Theological Libraries Month (October 2006) Pages (Printed from web site on 8/18/06), 2006 Oct (Box 12, Folder 457)
      - Theological Libraries Month, 2006, Actively Participating Institutions (Printed from web site on 10/13/06), 2006 Oct (Box 12, Folder 458)
      - Theological Libraries Month (October 2006) Success Stories (Printed from web site on 10/27/06), 2006 Oct (Box 12, Folder 459)
      - ATLA Press Releases, 2001-2006 (Printed from web site on 10/13/06) (Box 12, Folder 460)
  - Preservation Department
    - General
      - Advisory Consultation on a Project to Index and Preserve Periodical Literature in Religion, 1900-1948, 1991 Feb 6 (Box 12, Folder 462)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 1 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 463)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 1 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 464)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 2 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 465)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 2 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 466)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 3 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 467)
      - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase 3 Catalog: Listed in Author Order (Folder 2 of 2); flyer re. Phase 6: ATLA Denominational Documentation Series, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 468)
      - ATLA Serials on Microfilm Catalog, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 469)
      - Guide to Selections From the Day Missions Collection: Asia and the Pacific Rim, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 470)
      - ATLA Special Collection: Church History: Section One: Texts and Reference Works: Monograph Preservation Program Order List, 1992 Aug 3 (Box 12, Folder 471)
      - Preservation Filming in Religion (PREFIR), Fliers Regarding PREFIR Member Pricing, 1992 April and 1995 Dec 21 (Box 13, Folder 472)
      - Religious Monographs Preservation Project, Correspondence With Pew Charitable Trust, 1994 May -1996 Aug (Box 13, Folder 473)
      - Lilly Endowment Support of Preservation of Journal Literature in Religion, 1875-1950, Grant: Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 474)
      - Final Report to Lilly Endowment for the Grant Preservation of Journal Literature in Religion: 1875-1950, 1997 Feb 28 (Box 13, Folder 475)
      - Form letter to request publisher permission to distribute preservation microfilm, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 476)
      - Project Master Titles List: Serials Data Base, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Robert Allenson report on East Asian Pacific Religious Studies on Microfilm, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence regarding Mennonite periodicals, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Vendor Relationships
      - Correspondence with Sang Sul regarding agreement to film through his preservation microfilm company, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 477)
      - Microfilming agreement with Preservation Resources, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 478)
      - Microfilm Storage Proposal for ATLA with National Underground Storage (later called Iron Mountain), 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 479)
      - Christianity and the Encounter with World Religions Catalog From Scholarly Resources, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 480)
      - Christianity and the Encounter with World Religions Catalog From Scholarly Resources, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 481)
      - Scholarly Resources - Catalog, Agreements, Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 482)
      - Scholarly Resources Religious Studies Catalog, 2004 (Circa) (Box 13, Folder 483)
      - Thomson-Gale Catalog of ATLA Microform Products, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 484)
- Committees of the Association, 1990-2005; Series III
  - Committees Appointed by the Executive Director
    - Historical Records Committee / Archives Committee
      - Historical Records Committee Reports, Minutes, and Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 485)
      - Historical Records Committee Correspondence and Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 486)
      - Archives Committee: Agreement Between the Presbyterian Historical Society and ATLA Regarding Archives Care and Storage, 1998 Apr-May (Box 13, Folder 487)
      - Committee on Archives, Correspondence and Reports, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 548)
    - Annual Conference Committee
      - 1993 Conference Evaluations, 1993 Jul (Box 13, Folder 488)
      - 1993 Conference Evaluations, 1993 Jul (Box 13, Folder 489)
      - Correspondence, minutes, applications, conference evaluations, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 27-29)
    - Education Committee
      - Minutes, Agendas, and Follow-Up Correspondence (meeting), 1991 Dec 5-7 (Box 13, Folder 490)
      - Minutes, Agendas, and Follow-Up Correspondence (meeting), 1992 Oct 30-Nov 1 (Box 13, Folder 491)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 492)
      - Agenda and Notes (meetings), 1993 Jun and Oct (Box 13, Folder 493)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agenda Materials, 1994 Oct 20-21 (Box 13, Folder 494)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agenda Materials, 1995 Jun 13 (Box 13, Folder 495)
      - Meeting Agenda, Minutes, and Agenda Materials, 1995 Oct 6-7 (Box 13, Folder 496)
      - Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1996 Jun 20 (Box 13, Folder 497)
      - Meeting Agenda, Minutes, Agenda Materials, and Follow-up Correspondence, 1996 Oct 4-5 (Box 13, Folder 498)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 499)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 2001 Oct -2003 Jun (Box 13, Folder 500)
      - Description, Mandate, and List of Chairperson Duties, 1991-1997 (Box 13, Folder 501)
      - Education Committee Handbook, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 502)
      - Reports, Including Reports to the Board of Directors, 1992-2000 (Box 13, Folder 503)
      - Correspondence Regarding Work With Annual Conference Committee (ACC), 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 504)
      - Education Committee Budget, 1991-1998 (Box 13, Folder 505)
      - Evaluations of ATLA Annual Conferences, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 506)
      - Program Planning, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 507)
      - Programming Ideas Generated at Nashville Meeting, 1995 Sep-Oct (Box 13, Folder 508)
      - Reports on Conference Roundtables, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 509)
      - Evaluation of 1996 ATLA Institute, 1997 Apr 21 (Box 13, Folder 510)
      - Roundtables for the ATLA Annual Conference, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 511)
      - Programming Ideas, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 512)
      - Planning Materials for 2001 ATLA Conference Sessions, 2000 Aug -2001 Jun (Box 13, Folder 513)
      - Joint Planning Meeting With Annual Conference Committee Regarding 2002 ATLA Conference, 2001 Oct (Box 13, Folder 514)
      - Session Proposals and Feedback for 2002 ATLA Conference, 2000 Apr -2002 Jun (Box 13, Folder 515)
      - Regional Continuing Education Program Grant Guidelines, 1996 Circa (Box 13, Folder 516)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 517)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 518)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 519)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 520)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 521)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 522)
      - Regional Continuing Education Grants, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 523)
      - Correspondence Regarding Committee Membership, 1991-1996 (Box 13, Folder 524)
      - Related to ATLA Institutes, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 30-33)
      - Related to regional education workshops, 1994-1997 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Minutes, correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 3-7)
    - Financial Management Committee
      - Meeting notes, 1991 Jun (Box 14, Folder 609)
    - Local Host Committee
      - Preliminary Program and Registration Materials for 1991 ATLA Conference, 1991 Mar (Box 13, Folder 525)
      - Correspondence of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian of the 46th (1992) ATLA Conference, to ATLA Members, 1992 Apr-Jun (Box 13, Folder 526)
      - Conference Preparation materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, 46th (1992) ATLA Annual Conference (Box 13, Folder 527)
      - Banquet Preparation materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, 46th (1992) ATLA Annual Conference, 1992 Mar-Jun (Box 13, Folder 528)
      - Hotel Arrangement materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, 46th (1992) ATLA Annual Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 529)
      - Registration materials saved by Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 530)
      - Materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, Related to the Bridwell Library's Involvement in the 46th (1992) ATLA Annual Conference (Box 13, Folder 531)
      - Materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, Regarding 1992 Conference Tours (Box 13, Folder 532)
      - Materials of Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, regarding Rare Books Interest Group of the 1992 ATLA Annual Conference (Box 13, Folder 533)
      - Thank you letters sent to Roger Loyd, Host Librarian, 1992 ATLA Annual Conference, 1992 Jun (Box 13, Folder 534)
      - Minutes, corresponence, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Professional Development Committee
      - Seminar: Practical Personnel Management for the Theological Librarian, 2001 Jun 18 (Box 13, Folder 535)
      - Management Issues Seminar: The Library Budget, 2001 Jun-19 (Box 13, Folder 536)
      - Seminar: The Theological Library and the Educational Enterprise, 2003 Jun 24 (Box 13, Folder 537)
      - Meeting Materials, 1991 Apr 7-8 (Box 13, Folder 538)
    - Program Committee
      - Meeting Minutes and Agenda Items, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 539)
      - List of workshops, pre-conference sessions, rountables presented at ATLA annual conferences 1981-1996; minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Conference Evaluations for 1997 ATLA Annual Conference (Box 13, Folder 540)
    - Publications Committee
      - Publications Committee Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Joint Committees Established by the Board
    - ATS/ATLA Joint Committee Correspondence and Meeting Summaries, 1992-2003 (Box 13, Folder 542)
    - ATS/ATLA Digital Standards and Projects Committee. Suggestions for Meeting Topics, 2000 Mar (Box 13, Folder 543)
    - ATS/ATLA Digital Standards and Projects Committee. Minutes, reports, 2000-2004 (Box 14, Folder 612)
    - ATS/ATLA Digital Standards and Projects Committee: Cooperative Digital Resources Initiative (CDRI): Announcements of grants, Phases 1 – 4; article describing CDRI; brochure, flyer, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 613)
    - ATS/ATLA Digital Standards and Projects Committee: CDRI: Final Report to Henry Luce Foundation, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 614)
    - ATS/ATLA Digital Standards and Projects Committee: CDRI: "Metadata Requirements and Input for CDRI Projects", 2004 (Box 14, Folder 615)
  - Advisory Committees
    - Membership Advisory Committee
      - Establishment of committee, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Monographs Preservation Advisory Committee
      - Memos, reports, notes, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Preservation Advisory Committee
      - Records, 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 619)
      - Report, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Technology Advisory Committee
      - Records of Committee Member Mary Bischoff, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 544)
      - Records of Committee Member Mary Bischoff, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 545)
      - Agenda and Meeting Minutes, 1998 Jan 13-14 (Box 13, Folder 547)
      - Committee on Technology and Internet Planning: Correspondence Re: Internet Presence and Services Provided Through Vanderbilt, 1996 Feb-Jul (Box 13, Folder 546)
      - Planning and reports, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Meeting notes, 1994-1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Special Committees and Standing Committees of the Board
    - Nominating Committee: Correspondence of Committee Member Mary Bischoff, 1994 Jun-Jul (Box 13, Folder 549)
    - Tellers Committee, 1993/94 Board Election, 1993 Apr (Box 13, Folder 550)
    - Tellers Committee, 1994/95 Board Election, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Interest Groups, 1991-2004; Series IV
  - General
    - Interest Groups Flyer, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 551)
    - Policies and Procedures for ATLA Interest Groups, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 552)
    - Correspondence to Interest Group chairs, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Automation and Technology Section
    - Materials of the Group Chair Regarding 1995 ATLA Annual Conference Activities, 1994 Sep -1995 Apr (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Bib-base User's Group
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - College and University Section
    - Correspondence and Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 555)
    - Budget request, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Gay and Lesbian Professional Issues Interest Group/Forum
    - Tour of Gerber Library, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Judaica Interest Group
    - Proposal for Recognition of Judaica Interest Group, 1998 Jan 16 (Box 13, Folder 556)
  - OCLC Theological Users Group (TUG)
    - Mailing List, 1991 Jul (Box 13, Folder 557)
    - Application for Recognition of TUG and Letter Regarding Approval By Board, 1992 Jan-Feb (Box 13, Folder 558)
    - Newsletters, 1991 Jun -1992 Feb (Box 13, Folder 559)
  - Online Reference Resource Section
    - Correspondence Re: Establishment of Section, 1992 Jun-Jul (Box 13, Folder 560)
  - Public Services Steering Committee and Section
    - Meeting Minutes, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 561)
    - Draft ILL Code, 1993 Jul (Box 14, Folder 562)
    - Report of Virtual Reference Task Force, 2003 Dec (Box 14, Folder 616)
    - Publications Section
      - Bibliography of ATLA Members, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 563)
      - Information for section chairs, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Applications for awards, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Minutes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Roman Catholic Denominational Group
    - Newsletter, directories, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Special Collections Interest Group
    - Report, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Technical Services Division/Section
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    - Current LC Subject Headings in the Field of Religion, Volume 8, no. 2, 1991 Nov (Box 14, Folder 565)
    - Information and Meeting Agenda, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    - Newsletter, 1992 May (Box 14, Folder 567)
    - Theology Cataloging Bulletin, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 568)
    - Theology Cataloging Bulletin, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - TheologyCataloging Bulletin, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 24-31)
    - Theology Cataloging Bulletin, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 570)
- Affliated Institutions and Organizations, 1990-2004; Series V
  - General
    - Correspondence Regarding ATLA Partnerships/Commitments, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 571)
    - Correspondence Regarding Cooperation With Librarians and Libraries in Puerto Rico, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - All Africa Conference of Churches (AACC)
    - Correspondence Regarding Donation of ATLA Thesaurus, 1993 Jan-Apr (Box 14, Folder 573)
  - AAR/SBL
    - ATLA Representation at 1998 AAR/SBL Conference (Box 14, Folder 574)
  - Australian and New Zealand Theological Library Association (ANZTLA)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 575)
  - Catholic Library Association
    - 1997 Conference Presentation and Presentation Notes by Dennis Norlin, 1997 Apr (Box 14, Folder 576)
  - Charles University in Prague
    - Correspondence Regarding Indexing Czech Journals, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 577)
  - Conseil International des Associationś de Bibliothéques de Theologie (International Council of Theological Library Associations)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 578)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 579)
  - Bibliotheques Europeennes de Tehologie (BETH; formerly CONSEIL)
    - Correspondence, Conference Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 580)
    - BETH Brochures, 2004 (Circa.) (Box 14, Folder 581)
    - Agreement for Support of Sale of ATLA Religion Database, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 582)
  - Council of National Library and Information Associations
    - Appointment of ATLA Representative, 1992 Aug 5 (Box 14, Folder 583)
  - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR)
    - ATLA Sponsorship of CLIR, 1999 Jun -2001 Jun (Box 14, Folder 584)
  - Federacja Bibliotek Kóscielnych (FIDES)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 585)
  - International Association for Mission Studies (IAMS)
    - Database, Archives, and Bibliography (DABS) Interest Group, Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 586)
  - Overseas Council
    - Correspondence Regarding Donation of ATLA Print Indexes, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 587)
    - Donation of Religion Index One, Religion Index Two, and IBBR to Theological Schools in Developing Countries, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 588)